careersandeducation.com 2010-05-16

# Privacy Policy | Careersandeducation.com - Find Scholarships, Search Colleges and Universities, Find undergraduate and Graduate Degree Programs

**Privacy Policy Introduction:**   
We respect your privacy, security and user experience while visiting the Website - above all else. It is our sincere hope that your experience will be pleasant at www.Careersandeducation.com, and that the information we provide will be complete, accurate and very helpful to you and your family. 

After registering, you will receive a personal Confirmation email from our CEO. Be sure to save this email and mark www.Careersandeducation.com as a recognized sender in your email account in order to make sure emails from us reach your Inbox, and do not get caught in a Bulk Mail folder or accidentally deleted. 

**What This Privacy Policy Covers:**   
This Privacy Policy covers how we treat the information that we collect when you visit the Website. If you do not agree to the terms of this policy, please do not use this Website. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control. For example, our Website may contain links to other third party websites (such as those of our marketing partners or advertisers), which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the activities that take place on such websites. Please refer to those sites' own privacy policies to learn how they collect and use information about you. 

**A Special Note About Children:**   
We do not direct our Website to, nor do we knowingly collect any personal information from, children under the age of thirteen (13). If we learn that we have inadvertently received personal information from a child under the age of thirteen (13), we will promptly delete that information from our database. Please contact us if you believe we have received this type of information. See “How to Contact Us” section below. 

**Information Collection:

Registration with Careers & Education: 

**  
Non-Personal Information - When you visit our Website, our server logs collect non-personal information from you, including your IP address and the URL of the last site you viewed. 

Personal Information – When you register with Careersandeducation.com, we collect personal information from you, including your email address, name, postal address, phone number, gender, and date of birth. We do not request collect sensitive personal information such as your credit card number, bank account information or social security number in order to register with Careersandeducation.com; however, when you choose to complete an advertising form in the registration process for one of our advertisers this sensitive information may be requested by the advertiser and therefore collected by Careersandeducation.com for the sole purpose of providing this information to the advertiser. Careersandeducation.com does not store or use this information for any other purpose. During this process we ensure that this information is encrypted in transit using secure socket layer technology (SSL). Please see the Security section below for additional information. 

**Submitting Information during the Registration Process:**   
During the registration process you will be directed through a number of third party websites displaying advertisements for Universities, Education Programs and other Special Offers that may be of interest to you. If you select "Yes" on any of these advertisements or choose to complete the forms provided, you will be asked to submit personal information. On behalf of certain advertisers, we will request sensitive personal information such as your credit card number or social security number. In all cases, when you click on the Submit button we will securely transfer your personal information to the third-party advertiser you selected. We will not use the information that you submit for transfer to a third-party advertiser for our own purposes; nor will we retain or disclose it. You may be prompted by some advertisers to answer additional questions. These pages may be "co-branded" or "framed." This means that they may appear to be part of our Website because they have a Careersandeducation.com look and feel, but they are, in fact, part of the advertiser's site. All framed pages contain the following disclaimer at the bottom of the page: "*By submitting the form above I agree to provide this information to the advertiser and to be contacted by this advertiser directly." On these framed pages, we do not collect any of the additional information you submit; the advertiser does, and it does not share this information with us. The advertiser uses your information to deliver additional information to you about its particular product or service and perhaps for other purposes. Its collection and use of your information is subject to its own privacy policy. 

**Use of Cookies and Web Beacons:**   
Cookies - We use cookies to: (1) display the most appropriate advertising, based on your interests and activities, as expressed during your registration; (2) estimate our audience size; (3) measure our audience's traffic patterns; and (4) to pre-populate your personal information on third-party forms. We also use these cookies in order to save you time completing advertising forms in which you express an interest. You are always free to decline cookies, but by doing so you may not be able to use certain features of our Website or take full advantage of our offerings. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, erase cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. Each browser is different, so check the Help menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. 

Third-Party Cookies - To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place third parties' ads on our Website. These companies may set and access their own cookies on your computer. This means that, as a result of your visit to our Website, these companies may collect non-personally identifiable information from you, such as your domain type, your IP address and clicking behavior. These cookies are not connected to any of your personal information. These companies' collection and use of your information are subject to their own privacy policies. 

Web Beacons - We may use web beacons on the Website, in our advertisements on other sites and in e-mails. A web beacon is an electronic image that can be used to recognize a cookie on your computer when you view a web page or email. Web beacons allow us to recognize users by accessing our cookies. They help us measure the effectiveness of our site, our advertising and our email campaigns in various ways, for example, by counting the number of individuals who visit our site from a particular advertisement, as well as by telling us when a web page is viewed and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. 

Web beacons also help us count the number of individuals who open or act upon an email message. The information we collect may include personal information. We may also combine the information that we collect through web beacons with other personal information we have collected from you, such as your registration information. We use this information to respond to your questions (for example, if you do not remember registering on the Website or don't know how we received your email address). 

We also use this information to prevent fraud by members of our affiliate program and others. We will not share any personal information collected through our web beacons with any third party, except for service providers who act on our behalf and who are contractually prohibited from any other use or disclosure of the information. You can make some web beacons unusable by rejecting cookies. 

Third-Party Web Beacons - Members of our affiliate program may use web beacons to help us track the number of individuals the affiliate has directed to the Website. The web beacons used by our affiliate program members do not collect any personal information. 

**Information Use:

Registration with Careersandeducation.com:

**   
We may use the information we collect for any of the following purposes: (1) to administer sweepstakes and promotions on our Website and to notify winners; (2) to improve the content of our Website, (3) to customize the content and/or layout of our pages for each individual visitor, (4) to notify you about updates to our Website, (5) to conduct research, (6) to fulfill your requests for products and services, (7) to send you information and promotional materials and offers from us as well as from our affiliates, marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties, (8) to contact you when necessary, (9) to help address problems with our Website or marketing services, (10) to administer our Website, (11) to help us better understand visitors’ use of our Website, (12) to protect the security or integrity of our Website, (13) to deliver targeted display advertisements and offers to you, and (14) to enable our marketing partners, advertisers and other third parties to communicate with site visitors when you have agreed to be contacted by them directly. 

As described above under "Information Collection," some advertisers' pages may be "co-branded" or "framed." Although these pages have a Careersandeducation.com look and feel, Careersandeducation.com does not host these pages, and the information you submit on these pages is subject to the third-party advertiser’s own privacy policy. Any information you submit during the Registration Process after you leave our homepage is submitted by you directly to the third party advertiser and is used only by that advertiser, with your permission, to contact you or to provide you with additional information on the product or service in which you indicated an interest. Careersandeducation.com does not collect, receive or use this information for any reason. 

The web pages in our registration process are "Co-Branded Sites" operated by third parties who are trusted business partners of Careersandeducation.com. We have partnered with these companies in order to make their offerings available to you. Although these pages have a Careersandeducation.com look and feel, Careersandeducation.com does not host these pages, and the information you submit on these pages is subject to the third parties' own privacy statements. 

**Security:**   
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter a credit card number and/or social security number on our advertisers' pages or on our registration or order forms, we ensure that information is encrypted in transit using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link http://www.webopedia.com/TERM/S/SSL.html. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Information Sharing:**   
We share the information we collect from and about you as follows: We share your information with our employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries and service providers, if the disclosure will enable any of these entities to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us. For example, our service providers may use your personal information to deliver scholarship information, newsletters and special offers to you via email or postal mail. These third parties are not permitted to use your information for any secondary purpose. With your consent, we share your information with third parties for their use in marketing their own and/or their clients' products and services to you. For example, when you first register on the Website, we will ask you whether you would like to receive marketing communications from third parties. 

We will disclose your information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

We will disclose your information if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety or rights of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. We will transfer your information if all or part of our company or our operations are acquired by or merged with another company. In this instance, we will notify you as detailed in the "Changes to this Privacy Policy" section below. 

Wireless Privacy Policy:

We may use personal information to provide services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.  In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence.  You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.  If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.

Detailed Wireless Policy:  

Data obtained from you in connection with this SMS service may include your name, address, cell phone number, your provider's name, and the date, time, and content of your messages.  In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence.  All charges are billed by and payable to your mobile service provider.  We will not be liable for any delays in the receipt of any SMS messages, as delivery is subject to effective transmission from your network operator.  SMS message services are provided on an AS IS basis.

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising.  We may also use personal information for auditing, research and analysis to operate and improve our technologies and services.  We may share aggregated and non personal information with third parties outside of CareersandEducation.com.  When we use third parties to assist us in processing your personal information, we require that they comply with our Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  We may also share information with third parties in limited circumstances, including when complying with legal processes, preventing fraud or imminent harm, and ensuring the security of our network and services. 

You may remove your information from our database.  If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.  You may remove your information by sending your request in writing via email to privacy@innovationads.com, or sending "STOP", "END", "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received.  

 **Choice/Opt-Out:**

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt out of receiving them by clicking here, by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at privacy@innovationads.com. See the section below on "Access to Personally Identifiable Information" for additional information on how to unsubscribe from receiving these mailings. 

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party. If you wish to change the way a marketing partner contacts you, you must contact the marketing partner directly. 

**Tell-A-Friend Disclaimer:**  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit our site. Careersandeducation.com does not store this information. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information:**  
If your contact information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing Customer Support at IMWeb@innovationads.com, or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail using the contact information listed below. You can also opt out and remove your information from our database online by clicking here. Any personal information we provide to a marketing partner is subject to that marketing partner's own privacy policy. If you wish to change the way a marketing partner contacts you, you must contact the marketing partner directly. 

Your California Privacy Rights  
Under California law, site visitors who are residents of California may request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an e-mail to IMWeb@innovationads.com or write to us at Careers & Education, 233 Broadway, 21st Floor, New York, NY 10279. 

**How to Contact Us:**  
If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at: 

Careers & Education   
233 Broadway, 21st Floor   
New York, NY 10279   
(P) 212-509-5218   
(F) 866-272-5129   
IMWeb@innovationads.com 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy:**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
